var sAndVquestionBank = 
[
	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 1.  The correct answer is C",
		correct:"C",
		wrong:["A", "B", "D"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 2.  The correct answer is B",
		correct:"B",
		wrong:["A", "D", "C"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 3.  The correct answer is Boop",
		correct:"Boop",
		wrong:["Acid", "Dang", "Can"]
	},
	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 4.  The correct answer is C",
		correct:"C",
		wrong:["A", "B", "D"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 5.  The correct answer is B",
		correct:"B",
		wrong:["A", "D", "C"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 6.  The correct answer is Boop",
		correct:"Boop",
		wrong:["Acid", "Dang", "Can"]
	},
	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 7.  The correct answer is C",
		correct:"C",
		wrong:["A", "B", "D"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 8.  The correct answer is B",
		correct:"B",
		wrong:["A", "D", "C"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 9.  The correct answer is Boop",
		correct:"Boop",
		wrong:["Acid", "Dang", "Can"]
	},
	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 10.  The correct answer is C",
		correct:"C",
		wrong:["A", "B", "D"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 11.  The correct answer is B",
		correct:"B",
		wrong:["A", "D", "C"]
	},

	{
		type: "text",
		question:"1D Kinematics test question 12.  The correct answer is Boop",
		correct:"Boop",
		wrong:["Acid", "Dang", "Can"]
	}
]

database.ref("questions/1D Kinematics").update(
{
	"2 Distance and Displacement": sAndVquestionBank
})
